That Time I Got Reincarnated as a Slime
Episode 9: Attack of the Ogres
Rimuru and the Goblins' development of
their village continued to progress.
（リムル）
リムルたちの村の開発は
着々と進んでいた
Kaijin and the three Dwarf brothers,
Garm, Dord, and Myrd,
カイジン そして ドワーフ三兄弟の
ガルム ドルド ミルドが
made clothing and tools and built more homes,
衣類 道具作成 住居建設を進め
while the Goblin Lords under Rigurd worked
out a system for ruling the village.
リグルドの下(もと)
ゴブリン･ロードたちが
村の統治を行う流れが出来ていた
Everything's going great!
（リムル）
順調 順調
Even without my orders,
everyone's doing their job.
俺が指示しなくても それぞれが
ちゃんとやってくれてる
Makes it easier for me!
俺も楽できるし…
それに 俺には
Besides, there's something
important I need to do.
やらなければならない
大事なことがある
Good. No one's around.
（リムル）よし 誰もいないな
There, all fixed.
修理完了っと
Shizu-san, I'll take good
care of this keepsake of you.
シズさん… 形見 大切にするよ
さて…
Now, then...
フフフ… フハハ
Transform!
へ〜んしん！
Mimic -> Human
（リムル）ふむ…
This Mimic works really smoothly.
すごくスムーズに擬態できるな
An actual human body...
Feels great to have this.
人間の体だ… ありがたい
Vision...
視覚に…
聴覚
Hearing...
うん　ていうか…
Actually, I think I could see and
hear things better as a slime.
スライムのときのほうが
よく見えてたし よく聞こえてたな
Because of Magic Sense?
魔力感知の力か？
So, next...
次は…
なあ 大賢者(だいけんじゃ)
Hey, Great Sage, since I ate Ifrit,
イフリートを捕食したから
分身 俺も使えるのかな？
can I use body doubles now, too?
Answer.
（大賢者）
解(かい) “分身体”含め
Analysis Complete
All of Ifrit's skills, including
Body Double, have been analyzed.
イフリートの保有スキルは
解析完了しています
All of Ifrit's skills,
including
Body Double,
have been analyzed.
All right, great!
よしよし
じゃあ 早速 試してみるか
I'll try it out right now.
Body Double!
分身体！
Body Double
I see... It does look like Shizu-san.
なるほど シズさんに似ている
No trace at all of how I
looked when I was alive.
前世の俺の要素は かけらもないな
なんという
美少… 年(ねん)？　女(じょ)？
What a beautiful... boy? Girl?
（リムル）
人の姿になったときの性別を
確認しないわけにはいかないよな
Well, I need to know what sex my
body is when in human form, right?
Though I can kind of already tell...
まあ もう感覚で
なんとなく分かってんだけどさ
But since I didn't actually
check to be sure...
ちゃんと確認してなかったから…
My son didn't make it!
息子… 復活ならず
I seem rather androgynous...
しかも 中性…
In fact, I have no gender at all!
いや 性別がない
I'm sexless!
無性(むせい)だった
Well, I guess I had no
gender as a slime, anyway.
まあ スライムって時点で
性別とかなかったしな
あれ？　そういえば
Wait... Now that I think about it,
さっき人型に擬態するとき
黒い霧が出てなかったような…
when I took human form earlier,
I didn't see any black mist...
Answer.
Answer
When using Mimic to assume a
form larger than one's own,
（大賢者）
本体より体積の大きな存在へ
擬態する場合
black mist produced by magicule
consumption makes up the difference.
不足分を 魔素(まそ)を消費して作った
黒霧で補います
Black
Mist
Which means... I could
create an adult form, too!
てことは
大人の姿も作れるってことか
All right!
よし！
おお！　男寄りにできるか？
Ooh! Can I make it look masculine?
Hey, he's pretty handsome!
なかなかイケメンじゃないか！
Okay, now make it feminine!
じゃあ 次は女寄りに！
Ooh!
おお〜！　って…
Wait, stop! Stop! Go back!
ストップ！　ストップ！　戻れ
ハア ハア…
I can't do that.
Giving myself an adult female form
いかん… 大人の女性の姿にすると
シズさんぽくて背徳感が募(つの)る
makes me look like Shizu-san,
and that just feels immoral.
That concludes my report.
（リグルド）報告は以上であります
Okay, no problems. Good work.
（リムル）
ああ 問題ない　ご苦労さん
Oh, also...
（リグルド）ああ それと…
（リムル）ん？
今日も
お食事は必要ないのでありますか？
Are you sure you will
need no food again today?
Yeah, I can't taste anything
as a slime anywa—
ああ どうせスライムの体じゃ
味がしな…
おお〜 リグルド！
Rigurd!
Yes?
I'm gonna eat with you guys starting today!
今日から
僕も一緒にメシを食うことにする！
Truly?!
なんと！
Then we must prepare a lavish feast tonight!
では 今夜は宴会ですな
うむ 頼んだぞ！
Yeah, do that!
Yes, sir!
That's right! Since I can
mimic a human form now,
（リムル）
そうだよ
せっかく 人に
擬態できるようになったんだから
I'm gonna eat all kinds of tasty food!
おいしいご飯 食べまくってやる！
I wonder what's on the menu...
メニューは何だろう♪
Meat, maybe? There'll probably be meat.
肉かな？　肉だろうな〜
Which means I'll want rice, too...
となると 米も欲しいけど…
Do they have rice plants in this world?
この世界に稲ってあるのかな？
今度 探してみるか
I'll have to look for some eventually.
If I find any, I'll make some rice fields...
あったら 田んぼを作って…
Great Rimuru!
（リグル）リムル様！
Thanks for always getting our food for us.
（リムル）食料調達 ご苦労さん
Thank you, sir.
ありがとうございます
We're just on our way out to the forest.
これから森へ向かうところです
今夜は宴会の予定だ
おいしそうな獲物を頼むよ
We're having a feast tonight,
so bring back some tasty prey!
（ゴブタ）
今日はリムル様も
食べるっすか？
Are you going to eat with us today?
おうよ！　なんせ
この体には味覚があるからな
Sure am!
This body has a sense of taste, after all.
ほう…
If you eat a lot, I wonder if
your boobs will get bigger...
いっぱい食べたら
おっぱいも育つっすかね？
I'm sorry! I'll make sure
Gobta is strictly disciplined!
すみません！
ゴブタには
きっちりと教育しておきますので…
それから 特上の牛鹿(うじか)を
ご用意いたしましょう
Anyway, I will prepare some
grade-A bulldeer for the feast.
Bulldeer
Great! Thanks!
おう！　頼むな
Just leave it to me.
（リグル）お任せください！
Many magical beasts have been traveling
this way from deep in the forest, lately,
最近は 森の奥から移動してくる
魔獣が多いので
so prey is abundant.
獲物は豊富なんです
Did something happen?
何かあったのか？
No, magical beasts move from place
to place as the environment changes.
いえ 魔獣は環境の変化などで
移動したりしますからね
I don't think it's anything serious.
大したことないと思うのですが…
ふ〜ん…
You called, Master?
（ランガ）お呼びですか 我が主(あるじ)
Ranga, go into the forest with Rigur's team.
（リムル）
ランガ
リグルたちと森に同行してくれ
I doubt anything will happen,
but just in case.
何もないと思うけど
もしものときは頼む
Understood. You can count on me.
（ランガ）
心得ました　お任せください！
No need for reservation, Rigur.
Take me along.
遠慮はいらぬ
我を連れていけ リグル殿！
（リムル）
おお〜 かっこいいぞ ランガ
Wow, that was pretty cool, Ranga!
Even cooler if you weren't doing that...
それがなければ もっとな
I paid a visit to the cave
where Veldora had been sealed.
（リムル）
俺は ヴェルドラが封印されていた
洞窟にやって来た
I wanted to test out Degenerate,
シズさんから受け継いだ
ユニークスキル—
the unique skill I'd received from Shizu-san,
“変質者”の効果を
試しておこうと思ったのだ
in a place where it wouldn't disturb anyone.
誰の迷惑にもならない場所で
Regardless of the impression
given by the name "Degenerate,"
“変質者”は
字面(じづら)から受ける印象は ともかく
the skill was important to her,
and that makes it precious.
彼女の思いが込められた
大事な能力だ
The skill...
その能力とは…
Degenerate
uses unification and separation
to merge skills together,
統合と分離
さまざまなスキルを統合し
新しいスキルへと進化させ…
evolving them into new skills.
In other words, she used it
to gain a bunch of new skills.
つまりは
新しい能力がポンポンと獲得できた
One of them was...
そのひとつが…
What is this? It's creepy...
何これ… えげつない
This is the extra skill, Black Flame.
（大賢者）
エクストラスキル
〝黒炎(こくえん)〞です
— Black Flame —
I'll have to be careful
how I use this one, too.
これも使いどころを考えないとな
しかし…
Still...
ホントにシズさんには感謝しないと
I should really be grateful to Shizu-san.
This mask has the power
to suppress magic, right?
この仮面
魔力を抑える力があるんだよな
Let's see.
どれ…
How's this?
どうだ？
Answer.
Aura completely erased
The faint aura you were emitting
has been completely erased.
（大賢者）
わずかに漏れ出ていたオーラが
完全に消滅しました
In this state, you would
be perceived as a human.
この状態ならば
“人間”と認識されるでしょう
Magicule Level: 0
Perception: Human
Okay. I should wear this
when I go to new places.
（リムル）
よし 対外向けには
この格好で出向くことにしよう
Lookin' good!
似合うな
（大賢者）
はい
Right.
You sound unimpressed.
（リムル）淡泊だな…
Great Rimuru!
（ランガ）リムル様！
（リムル）あっ…
Receiving Thought Communication from: Ranga.
（大賢者）
個体名ランガからの思念伝達
Tempest Wolf
Thought Communication: Ranga
Vocal tone indicates that
it is a request for aid.
声音から救援要請と推測
Tempest Wolf
Likely a request for aid
やあ！
だあ〜！　うっ…
I'm gonna die! I'm dead!
死んじゃうっす〜
ハア ハア…
What happened?!
（リムル）どうした？
斬られたっす！　超痛いっす！
I got cut! It hurts so bad!
Calm down. It's not deep.
（リムル）落ち着け 傷は浅いぞ
Who are you guys?
何だ？　お前ら
Wait... Great Rimuru, it's you!
あっ リムル様じゃないっすか！
You got worried and came to help?
心配になったから
来てくれたんすね？
Yeah, that's right.
（リムル）ああ そうだな
You seem fine, so I guess
you don't need any potion.
元気そうだし
回復薬はいらないみたいだな
W-Wait! I want some!
（ゴブタ）
ちょ… ちょっと！　欲しいっす！
I'm sorry I joked around like that!
冗談言って すまなかったっすよ…
あ… たっ 助かったっす
Th-That helped a lot!
（リムル）ランガ！
Ranga!
Master, forgive me.
（ランガ）
主よ 申し訳ありません
我がいながら このような…
This happened while I was here...
Come back, Rigur!
（リムル）戻れ リグル！
G-Great Rimuru... I am sorry.
（リグル）
リ… リムル様 申し訳ありません
Don't worry. Leave this
to me and get some rest.
（リムル）
安心しろ
あとは俺に任せて ゆっくり休め
Thank you...
ありがとうございます…
Ranga, what happened to
the ones who've fallen?
（リムル）
ランガ この倒れている者たちは
どうした？
They've been put to sleep with magic.
（ランガ）
はっ
魔法により眠らされております
あの桃色の髪の仕業です
That pink-haired one did it.
Magic, huh?
（リムル）魔法か…
Looks like these guys are gonna be trouble.
なかなか
やっかいな相手らしいな
How humiliating. I never thought
we would run into Ogres.
面目ありません
まさか
オーガに出くわすとは思わず…
Ogres?
（リムル）オーガ？
The ones in games and
movies look like this...
（リムル）
ゲームや映画だと
こんなイメージ…
ウ〜ガ〜！
But these don't look like that at all.
（リムル）
だったけど 随分 違うんだな
They even have armor on.
なんか 鎧(よろい)までつけてるし…
Also, those look like
Japanese swords to me...
ていうか
どう見ても日本刀だよな あれ
Six Ogres...
６人のオーガか…
Hey, you guys.
（リムル）おい お前ら
I don't know what happened,
but sorry about what my guys did.
事情は知らんが
うちのヤツらが失礼したな
Would you be willing to talk this out?
話し合いに応じる気はあるか？
They're clearly much stronger,
（リムル）
実力差は明白なのに
but Gobta and Rigur weren't fatally wounded,
ゴブタもリグルも
致命傷ではなかったし
and most of our security force was
just put to sleep, not injured.
警備隊のほとんどは
無傷で無力化されてる
There must be something to it...
なんか訳ありか？
Well, I'll just have to be
the adult in the room and—
まっ ここは
こちらが大人の対応を…
Show us who you really are, evil majin!
（男オーガ）
正体を現せ 邪悪な魔人め！
Huh?
Hey, hang on! What did you call me?
おいおい ちょっと待て
俺が 何だって？
（男オーガ）魔物を使役するなど
Enslaving monsters is not a feat
just any human can accomplish.
普通の人間にできる
芸当ではあるまい
Huh?
見た目を偽り オーラを
抑えているようだが甘いわ！
You may hide your appearance and
suppress your aura, but it won't work!
Reveal your true identity.
（老オーガ）正体を現すがいい
黒幕から出向いてくれるとは
好都合というもの
For the mastermind to approach
us himself is most convenient.
Yikes!
（リムル）
ガ〜ン！
But my true identity is
just a lovable slime...
俺の正体なんて
ただの愛くるしいスライムなのに…
Hey, listen, guys...
（リムル）なあ あのな…
フン！
貴様の言葉など聞く耳を持たん
We have no intention of listening to you.
That mask tells us everything
we need to know!
全て その仮面が物語っている！
（リムル）は？　仮面…
My mask?
Wait a minute! Aren't you
making some kind of mistake?
待ってくれ
何か勘違いしてないか？
This is just a keepsake of—
これは ある人の形見で…
If it will serve to repay even
a billionth of what was done
（男オーガ）
同胞の無念 その億分の１でも
貴様の首で あがなってもらおう！
to our brethren, we will have your head!
邪悪なる豚どもの仲間め！
You friend of those evil pigs!
What shall we do?
（ランガ）どういたしますか？
Do? I mean...
（リムル）どうって…
You take care of the pink-haired one.
お前は あの桃色を相手しろ
Yes, sir.
And don't kill her.
（リムル）決して殺すなよ
Yes, sir.
I think there's more to this.
（リムル）どうも裏がありそうだ
Just get in their way a bit.
邪魔だけしてくれればいいから
残りは俺が倒すよ
I'll take out the rest.
But that would mean you'd
be taking on five Ogres...
（ランガ）
しかし リムル様が
オーガ５体を相手することに…
Not a problem.
（リムル）
問題ない　負ける気がしない
I won't lose.
That's my master!
（ランガ）
さすがは我が主！　承知！
Understood!
You underestimate us.
ナメられたものだな
Are you truly brave or just foolhardy?
真の勇気か ただの蛮勇か
Out of respect for your sheer nerve,
I'll go along with your provocation.
その度胸に敬意を払い
挑発に乗ってやろう
I hope you don't regret it later.
後悔するなよ
（オーガ）ふん！
（リムル）お前は眠っとけ
You can just take a nap.
— Paralysis Breath —
（リムル）おっと！
Sorry, but I saw you with Magic Sense.
悪いな 魔力感知で丸見えだ
（リムル）
デカい！
Huge!
Wait, that's not what I meant by "I saw you!"
（リムル）
いや 丸見えってのは
そういう意味じゃないぞ
Don't get me wrong!
誤解するな
Looks like you're about to fall, miss.
（リムル）
転びそうですよ
お嬢さん
Sticky Steel Thread
Joke!
（リムル）
なんちゃって
— Body Armor —
（リグル）おお…
（ゴブタ）さすがっす！
Way to go!
（ランガのうなり声）
（女オーガ）あんなに簡単に…
He beat us that easily?
So, that just leaves...
（リムル）さて あとは…
What'll it be?
どうする？
（老オーガ）むう…
The Evil Centipede's Paralysis Breath...
エビルムカデの“麻痺(まひ)吐息”
The Black Spider's Sticky Steel Thread...
ブラックスパイダーの
“粘糸(ねんし)”“鋼糸(こうし)”
The Armorsaurus's Body Armor...
アーマーサウルスの“身体装甲”
He may have learned the skills
of many other monsters, as well.
（老オーガ）
ほかにも多数の魔物の技を
体得しているやもしれません
Do not lower your guard, young master.
ご油断めされるな 若
He named all the skills I used,
（リムル）
あのじいさん 俺が捕食した魔物と
獲得したスキルを
and the monsters they came
from, from just one look...
ひと目 見ただけで
言い当てやがった
I should try not to give too much away.
手の内を見せ過ぎるのは
マズいかもな
Can we stop this?
（リムル）ここら辺にしないか？
I'd like you to hear what I have to say now.
そろそろ
俺の言い分も聞いてほしいんだが…
Quiet, evil majin!
黙れ！　邪悪な魔人め
Okay, um... So, listen...
（リムル）え〜っと だからな…
I admit you are strong.
確かに貴様は強い
That makes me all the more certain.
だからこそ 確信が深まった
Certain of what?
（リムル）確信？
やはり 貴様はヤツらの仲間だ！
You are one of them!
Them? Who?
（リムル）ヤツらって…
It is unthinkable for us Ogres
to be defeated by mere Orcs!
（男オーガ）
たかがオークごときに
我らオーガが敗れるなど考えられぬ
Orc?
（リムル）オーク？
H-Hang on, what makes you—
おっ おい さっきから何を…
Quiet!
黙れ！
I know it was all the work of
you and your majin comrades!
全ては 貴様ら
魔人の仕業なのだろうが！
Huh? Majin?
（リムル）えっ 魔人？
とぼけるな！
Don't deny it!
Wait! You've got the wrong—
（リムル）待てよ それは誤解…
（老オーガ）
む… わしも もうろくしたものよ
I must be going senile.
I was certain I cut off your head.
頭をはねたと思ったのじゃが
Are they serious?
（リムル）
マジかよ…
リムル様！
Great Rimuru!
Y-Your arm!
うっ 腕が…
Master!
（ランガ）我が主！
（リムル）
こっちはいい！　油断するな
I'm fine! Don't let your guard down!
Did he get under my Magic Sense
（リムル）
魔力感知をかいくぐり
and easily break through my
Multilayer Barrier and Body Armor?
多重結界と身体装甲を
あっさり破ったのか？
Next time, I won't miss.
（老オーガ）次は外さんぞ！
Looks like you were just foolhardy after all.
どうやら蛮勇のほうだったようだな
右腕を失い発狂しない胆力(たんりょく)は
褒めてやる
I commend your courage to remain
calm after losing an arm.
一人で俺たちを相手取ろうとした
その傲慢さが貴様の敗因だ
The pride that compelled you to take
us all on alone will be your downfall!
冥府で悔やみ続けるがいい！
Regret your folly in the next life!
— Ultraspeed Regeneration —
Did you think you'd beaten me just
by cutting off one of my arms?
片手を斬り落とした程度で
俺に勝ったつもりだったのか？
ば… 化け物め！
F-Foul beast!
Ogre Flame!
オーガフレイム！
Young master...
（老オーガ）若…
Did I... get him?
やった… のか？
Too bad.
（リムル）
残念だったな
俺に炎は効かないんだ
Fire has no effect on me.
You were right, though.
だが 確かに俺は
お前たちを甘く見ていたようだ
I did underestimate you.
I'll show you...
少し…
本気を見せてやろう
what I'm like when I'm serious.
What an aura...
（老オーガ）なんというオーラ…
Take a good look.
よく見ておけ
— Black Flame —
That's... That flame is...
（女オーガ）
あっ あれは… あの炎は…
It's not produced by using
the surrounding magicules!
周囲の魔素を利用した
妖術ではありませぬ！
The only thing forming that
flame is his pure strength!
あの炎を形作っているのは
純粋に あの者の力のみ
And the size of the flame mirrors
the size of his power...
炎の大きさが
そのまま あの者の力…
もっと面白いものを
見せてやろう
I'll show you something
even more interesting.
これが俺の真の力だ！
This is my true power!
Uh...
（リムル）
やっぱ 封印しといたままのほうが
いいかな これ…
Maybe I should've kept this
one under wraps, after all...
What now? Still want to fight?
どうする？　まだやるか？
（リムル）
よしよし ビビってるな
頼むから これで降参してくれよ
Good, he's scared.
Please just surrender now!
Young master, please take
the princess and flee.
（老オーガ）
若 姫を連れて お逃げください
ここは わしが…
I will end this.
黙れ じい
Quiet, old man.
That is intense.
すさまじいな…
It saddens me to say it, but it
seems we are no match for you.
悲しいが
我らでは貴様に遠く及ばぬようだ
Still, I have my pride as the next
leader of the powerful Ogre clan!
だが 俺も 力ある種族…
オーガの次期頭領として育てられた
誇りがある
無念に散った同胞の恨みを
晴らさずして 何が頭領か！
And what leader would fail to
avenge his slain brethren?!
Even if I can't win, I will still fight back!
かなわぬまでも
一矢報いてくれるわ
Young master, if you fight,
I will fight by your side!
（老オーガ）
若… それでは わしも
お供いたしましょうぞ！
That's their answer?
（リムル）
そうきたか… マズいな
完全に裏目に出てしまった
Well, damn. That backfired on me.
（女オーガ）ハア ハア…
お待ちください お兄様！
Wait, Brother!
This individual may not be our enemy!
この方は
敵ではないかもしれません
Move!
そこをどけ！
No!
（女オーガ）いいえ！
（男オーガ）なぜだ！
Why?
He's a masked majin, just like
the one who attacked our village!
里を襲ったヤツと同じく
仮面をつけた魔人ではないか！
お前も そう言っただろう？
You said so yourself...
はい…
Yes... but please, try to
think this through calmly.
ですが
冷静になって考えてみてください
Why would such a powerful majin
use such underhanded tactics
これだけの力のある魔人様が
姑息(こそく)な手段を用いて
as forcing the pigs to attack our village?
豚どもに我らが里を襲撃させるなど
不自然です
It makes no sense.
それこそ お一人で我ら全てを
皆殺しにできましょうから
He surely has the power to kill us
all on his own, if he so desired!
There is no doubt he is unlike us,
この方が異質なのは
間違いありませんが
but I don't think he has any connection
to the ones that attacked our village.
恐らくは 里を襲った者どもとは
無関係なのではないかと
少しは人の話を聞く気になったか？
Feeling a little more willing to listen now?
I don't need this anymore, right?
もう これ いらないよな
Who are you?
何者なんだ お前は
Me?
俺？　俺は ただのスライムだよ
I'm just a slime.
A slime?
スライム？
Yep. Rimuru the slime.
そっ スライムのリムル
I-It's true...
ホッ ホントに…
And this mask is a keepsake
from someone I knew.
（リムル）
ちなみに この仮面は
ある人の形見だ
Feel free to see for yourself
whether it's the same one
なんなら
お前の里を襲ったヤツのと同じか
that your attacker had.
確認してもらってかまわない
All right...
似ている気はするが…
It does seem similar, but...
This one contains anti-magic power.
（女オーガ）
これには
抗魔の力が備わっているようです
（老オーガ）
しかし… あのときの魔人は
オーラを隠してはおらなんだな
But the majin from back then
wasn't concealing their aura...
では…
Then...
申し訳ない
Forgive us.
どうやら追い詰められて
勘違いしてしまったようだ
It seems our desperation caused
a grave misunderstanding.
Please accept my apology.
どうか謝罪を受け入れてほしい
Sure, I accept.
（リムル）うむ 苦しゅうない
Sheesh.
（リムル）
やれやれ
一時は どうなることかと思った
For a minute there, I wasn't
sure what was gonna happen.
（リムル）
まあ ここで話すのもなんだし
ひとまず村に戻ろうか
Well, this is no place to talk.
Let's head back to the village.
Come with us.
お前たちも来いよ
（男オーガ）あ… いいのか？
Are you sure?
（リムル）
うん いろいろ事情も聞きたいしな
Yep.
I want to hear about what
you've been through.
But we wounded your companions.
そちらの仲間を
傷つけてしまったが…
And we did the same to yours.
（リムル）
そりゃあ お互いさまだしな
But no one died, so we'll say it's all good.
死人は出なかったんだし
よしとしよう
Forgive us.
（老オーガ）すまんかったのう
（ゴブタ）ひい！
Besides, we're having a feast today.
（リムル）
それに 今日 うちは宴会なんだ！
人数が多いほうが楽しいだろ
The more, the merrier, right?
And so, the battle that began before
anyone even knew why had ended.
（リムル）
こうして 理由も分からずに
始まった争いは終わった
The Ogre princess reversed the sleep spell,
オーガの姫が昏睡(こんすい)の魔法を解除し
ゴブリンたちは目覚めた
and the Goblins awoke.
Rimuru healed the Ogres'
wounds with his potion,
オーガたちのケガは
リムルの回復薬で治し
and the whole gang headed for
Rimuru and the Goblins' village.
一同は リムルたちの村へと
向かったのだった
By the way, what's your name.
（リムル）そういえば 名前は？
Oh, we have no names.
いや 俺たちにネームドはいないよ
Oh, yeah. I forgot, most of you don't.
（リムル）
そっか 普通はないんだっけ…
That's right...
そっか
そっかあ…
Next time, "The Orc Lord."
（大賢者）
次回「オークロード」
The Orc Lord